Hello Hello Friends Welcome to Make Nikle Tech
Hindi Friends, through my videos I
try to give you
all kinds of information, big or small, related to vehicles.
Now the dry term for vehicles
is Road Side Assistant, which we
call RSSB. So if you have a two
wheeler, four wheeler or any other
vehicle, then you should have
good knowledge about RSSB so that at any
time, if your vehicle breaks down at any difficult place,
when there is an add-on, then you
can take advantage of it. So, I will talk about this
further,
watch the video completely. If you are new to the channel, then
definitely subscribe to the channel. Tap on the official side effect of Nikle
Tech Hindi. I will give the
description of this video, so please
download the app as well. Now
see, we all know that
according to tow law in India, to drive a vehicle, there should be
a valid insurance policy of the vehicle
and when we
buy the insurance policy of our vehicle, whether it is
online or offline, then the
people reaching there would not know about the
add-on also.  It
means that there are some additional features
that we can add to our policy and
take advantage of them. Now these additional
features include zero depression cover,
personal accident cover, driver cover, passenger
cover, electrical accessories cover, non-
electrical acid discover and one such
addition is roadside assistance cover.
You will see a lot of polishing, in some it is
written assistant off road.
In many policies, emergency assistant cover is
written. Now see, no matter what the name is
written, it does not mean that
you will get roadside assistance
with your insurance policy. Now see,
what all things are covered in road distance covered.
First, I will tell you this agreement, after that
I will tell you that it works completely like this.
Now see friends, there are
many such people who
carry on their work a lot, they keep driving continuously from one city
to another.
Okay, and many times it also happens that when we
buy a car, there is
not a service center for that car near us in our city, our village, so
whatever the situation may be, now such a question may arise
that  Your car may get damaged anywhere on the road,
okay now what all can happen in a bowl, it
could be that the
factory staff's car does not go, the battery is
not charging, the car is not starting with the battery saver, it
could be that the
tyre is punctured, it could also be
that you accidentally left your car
on the bike, that is,
you have lost the key, it could also be that
your car has some minor problem which can be
fixed on the road, it could also be that
your car has met with an accident,
then some major problem has come up due to which
you have to tow the car
to the service center, along with this there is
another thing here that this will be taken to the medical,
okay you should need medical assistant
or you should need fuel assistant,
not the petrol and diesel of your car has
run out somewhere on the way,
then you can avail the benefit of all these things from the
roadside assistance cover,
every
30p. Now you have to go to the road and go to the place where the
accident is in trouble, where there is a problem
You are going to get all this by going to all those places,
but here I will share some things
that it is not like that you call the company every two days
and say that the petrol is over, the petrol
is punctured, you will
not get a replacement there, basically it happens
twice, three, four or
five times in a year, every company has a different role, so at that
time you can take advantage of all this in a year, I will
sell it to you, that if you call sitting at home and say that the
petrol is over, then the company will
not provide petrol, basically it is an
emergency cover, so if there is a
backbone at some place where all the facilities are
not available, then you can take advantage, it is
from 28 now, let me explain how it works,
basically when we
buy any insurance policy, then the
toll free number of the company is also given there, so
if you ever get half an inch
damaged, then simply
call the company, after calling,
tell the details as per your insurance policy,
after that the company will make all the arrangements on
its own and whatever layer  Etc. whatever Aishwarya does
because the tension has to go, it will be delivered to your place, so this is
how it works,
now the question is how much money does it cost,
for this I will tell you that it costs very
little,
according to the amount of fat you have got, it takes very little pressure,
basically the ad and from this it is
₹40 rs. 80 100 200 500 around this, that is,
from 50 to the councilors, the company makes
around this, I just don't have to, just
pay this much in a year, just
₹50 ₹100, there is never an end, 100 200 to
500 1000 is around this, okay, then try
different companies and see which
company you are taking, but don't forget that much, you
can see that you are going to get a lot of fat in very less money,
I am
also saying that after seeing the boy here, it is not that all over
India these things are news, you are in chappal on massage, I
live in Ranchi,  The city
in which you live, where you have
taken the insurance, you have registered there, so from there,
every company has its
own limit of 500 kilometers, so in this series, all these
things like Bigg Boss service are covered,
so find out from the company from which you are going to take the loan, then
what is there and how much area does it cover,
some are kilometers, some are 500
kilometers, so friends,
many people do not have this information, but let me
tell you that spending very little money, you
get a lot from this, so if you
want, then next time when you take an insurance policy for
your bike, car or any other vehicle, then
you must add this there, I
hope that you got to learn something new through the information seen in this video, if you
liked the video, then do like and share it,
after the video, and do tell
me your opinion about the channel by commenting,
apart from this, if you are new to the channel or
you have not yet subscribed to the channel, then
please subscribe to the channel and
press the bell icon so that
you get updates on upcoming videos.  Keep getting in touch through notifications. See you
in the next video. Thanks
for watching this video. Goodbye.